The only thing getting blown tonight is their cover.
21 Jump Street is a action, comedy, crime film directed by Phil Lord.
When cops Schmidt and Jenko join the secret Jump Street unit, they use their
youthful appearances to go undercover as high school students.
They trade in their guns and badges for backpacks, and set
out to shut down a dangerous drug ring.
But, as time goes on, Schmidt and Jenko discover that high school is nothing like it was just a few years earlier -- and,
what's more, they must again confront the teenage terror and anxiety they thought they had left behind.
Schmidt, played by Jonah Hill.
Jenko, played by Channing Tatum.
Molly Tracey, played by Brie Larson.
Eric Molson, played by Dave Franco.
Mr. Walters, played by Rob Riggle.
Domingo, played by DeRay Davis.
21 Jump Street is a 2012 American buddy cop action comedy film directed by Phil Lord and Christopher
Miller in their live-action directorial debuts and written by Jonah Hill and Michael Bacall.
The film stars Hill and Channing Tatum in the lead roles, alongside
Brie Larson, Dave Franco, Rob Riggle, and Ice Cube.
It is an adaptation of  the 1987–1991 television
series of the same name by Stephen J.
Cannell and Patrick Hasburgh.
In the film, police officers Schmidt and Jenko are forced to relive high school when they are
assigned to prevent the outbreak of a new synthetic drug and arrest the supplier.
21 Jump Street was produced by Columbia Pictures, Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer
Pictures, Relativity Media, Original Film, and SJC Studios.
It premiered in SXSW festival on March 12, 2012, and was theatrically released in the United States four days later on March 16 by Sony Pictures Releasing where the
film received positive reviews from critics, with praise for its humor and the chemistry between Hill and Tatum, and then grossing $201 million worldwide.
A sequel, 22 Jump Street, was released on June 13, 2014, and in 2015 a female-led spin-off was in
development with main stars cast in 2018 and the first draft completed in 2020.
The film explores themes of drug dealer, high school,
investigation, nerd, male friendship.
The tone is lighthearted.